# Oritsegbemi Silver Okorodudu

#### Frontend Engineer / mimiokorodudu33@gmail.com

Oritsegbemi is an Engineering graduate with BSc in Computer Engineering. She has knowledge and experience using HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap and Figma. She is looking for opportunities in your organization to contribute and expand her knowledge and skills. She is currently an intern at spacepen technology.

### Career summary

## **Spacepen Technologies, Remote** – *Frontend intern*

FEBURARY 2022 - PRESENT

Key responsibilities

- Worked in a team to build the Company landing page
- Fix bugs
- Writes readable HTML, CSS and JavaScript codes
- Compile team monthly and weekly report

#### Data Plus Interactive, Abuja - Content Writer

MARCH 2021 - FEBURARY 2022

Key responsibilities

- Provided recommendations for the company website, wrote new content and edited existing content.
- Work in small and large workgroups to create, approve and audit documentation of any work done. Also interfacing with the task groups, support groups, topic specialists, and aiding colleagues in understanding the content of created materials.
- Write, proofread and edit high-quality training modules individually and as amember of the internal quality control team.

#### **Nadia Bakery, Benin City** –*Cashier/Content Developer*

AUGUST 2020 - MARCH 2021

- Wrote, Improved and Optimized over 12% of the content on the company's social media pages including adding the bakery to an online directory and developed its content.
- Created content for the social media campaigns ads.
- Managed the company's social media pages, created content and improved overall online presence by 120%.

- Processed about 45% of all debit card and cash transactions daily.
- Provided comprehensive solutions to customers' complaints and issues.

## Independent National Electoral Commission, Benin City - Ad-Hoc Staff

FEBRUARY 2018 - APRIL 2018

 Worked as an assistant polling officer in charge of verification and statistics for the 2018 election.

Lee Engineering, Warri - Engineering Intern

MARCH 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Responsible for maintenance of the company's hardware and installation of software.

#### Education

The University of Benin, Benin City - B. Eng Computer Engineering

January 2015 - December 2019.

Obtained my bachelor's degree in computer engineering in 2019 with a SecondClass Lower Division.

The University of Benin, Benin City - Dip. Maritime Engineering

2012 - 2014.

Obtained a Merit diploma in marine engineering from the faculty of engineering in 2014.

Skills

**Programming:** HTML, JavaScript, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap.

Design: UI/UX

Software: MS Office, Figma, VScode Editor, Git.